I have watched every E3 since 2008, and it has been a complete waste of time.
And it's going to be!
For the next sixty years!
But don't worry!
I'm going to save you from it.
EA decided to go first, because they wanted to get it over with.
They started with Titanfall, and there is a singleplayer now.
The main character is Jack Cooper, and this is what he looks like.
It's like they tried to make him forgettable for people with photographic memory.
Then they showed this...
I don't know what's going on here.
BioWare came out and said:
"In Mass Effect Andromeda you travel to the Andromeda galaxy to find new things to fuck!"
"We've already mated with the entire Milky Way!"
Chat started to freak out because it was FIFA time,
And now FIFA has coaches.
Good for you.
And they announced a new singleplayer campaign,
Which, honestly, biggest surprise of E3.
But no-one cares about some random footballer.
Hey, EA!
It's in the name!
I want to play as a FIFA executive.
Instead of the trailer voice saying "I've never seen a new guy attract this much interest."
He would instead say:
"I've never seen a new guy hide this much money."
Though Battlefield 1 looks great, and I'm very much looking forward to how they will fuck this up.
Ten out of ten.
So they announced a new Quake, but it's a sci-fi FPS,
And I'm tired of those, so I hope they change the settings to like, World War 1.
They showed some Heartstone, and then Todd shows up and says this:
TODD: There is something else though, that you've been asking us about, and yes, we've been working on it.
And then the music starts, and it's Skyrim remastered.
Okay.
Future city!
A man wakes up several times, and his eye gets redder and redder.
Then he cleans his sheets, and it gets better.
Prey.
Doom is great, everyone loves us.
Uh, yeah, yes.
Elder Scrolls Online is great, and everyo-
No, Bethesda! No!
Show continued with Dishonored 2 for twenty minutes.
I am exited for Dishonored 2, but now twenty minutes exited.
Then everything went black, and a roman six appeared.
And the crowd went insane.
Therefore, 100 out of 100.
Kind of feel bad for Phil Spencer.
Supposedly when he took over from Mattrick(?)
Half the Xbox headquarters didn't have electricity,
And the design department had been taken over by a grizzly bear.
But now that that had been sorted out they could finally redesign the Xbox.
We got bombarded with games.
They showed us the usual Xbox games and kept telling us that we would also get them on Windows 10.
Which is great, but then what's the point of buying an Xbone?
There was an epic crab game.
With the worst protagonist ever.
The game is not out yet, but this fucker has already ruined it.
Microsoft ended the conference like they started it.
By announcing a new Xbox One.
Another new Xbox One.
A+.
So the PC conference wasn't shit.
They showed a bunch of fun and interesting games.
Mount and Blade 2 looks like a pretty good PS2 game.
Only gonna spend 150 hours on it.
They showed a new Dark Souls game, made by the people who made Life is Strange.
I can see it.
At two hours and 21 minutes, it's a bit long.
But you did good, Nvidia.
4K out of 4K.
Ubisoft press conferences have been used in Quantamo.
I was worried that they might've learned something, but then it started with a dance number.
In the new Ghost Recon Mexicans have conquered Bolivia.
Should have built a wall.
More South Park!
Awesome!
More The Division!
Huh.
Famous for being the only online game where you can use Cheat Engine.
Watch Dogs 2 does not have unbelievable graphics.
And knowing Ubisoft, how bad will this game look?
Are we getting full motion video?
I didn't cringe enough with this press conference, so I'm giving it a Syndicate out of a Brotherhood.
Sony press conference was a complete waste of time,
Because they didn't talk about the Vita.
They announced The Last of War.
Kratos has moved here.
And now he's going to kill Thor and Loki.
Sorry to disappoint you, but Marvel already did that.
Then they announced The Last of Motorcycles.
And they showed a new trailer for The Last Guardian.
And a release date!
I don't believe you.
I am interested in both robot Witcher and robot Heavy Rain, and-
Oh my god, it's happening!
I am going to burn this house to the ground!
This is what they are turning Resident Evil into.
But I thought you were on the right path with-
Ha ha ha!
Weirdest trailer ever, and Playstation VR is going to cost 399$.
Which will be a cheap alternative for those who don't care about porn.
Which is no-one.
Wow, this looks amazing! Like, holy shit!
Oh, the press conference is over.
Well, I can honestly say that that was the best one Nintendo has ever made.